great news dudes I'm your new coach
aren't you our equipment manager nope
coach Randy had to flee the country I
got a promotion hey what y'all looking
at
I got this supplement at the story the
other day and we just want to know if
it's okay to take give me that
says is the newest scientific
breakthrough seems safe to me and have
you booked our hotel for next week I
gotta update my whereabouts where what
oh so you probably don't know what a TUV
is right oh of course I do that's a
Tuesday game guys I wouldn't worry about
that stuff anyways probably doesn't
matter
wrong ball coach
es can and should help them with that
check out coaches advantage to learn the
rules and avoid chaos like me
[Music]